<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Diary</string>
    <string name="diary_description">
        This Diary Application is a vault for your daily life experiences, ideas, and journal. Writing down is a therapy on its own way! Set a reminder to update your diary!
    </string>

    <string name="about_diary_header">
        "Unveiling the Enchanted Chronicles of this Ethereal Diary Realm!"
    </string>

    <string name="about_diary">
        "Brace yourselves, fellow voyagers, for I am on the cusp of unraveling"
            " the mystique that shrouds the essence of the MyDiary application! Firstly, "
            "let us extend a triumphant felicitation unto you for gracing this realm."
            " Your presence here, my dear luminary, is akin to stumbling upon an elusive "
            "comet's tail – an occurrence rarer than a sapphire amidst gravel. Within you "
            "lies a reservoir of latent potency yearning for liberation! But enough preamble; "
            "let us embark on this exhilarating odyssey together!"
            "Picture, if you will, the icy expanse of the austere southern pole – an "
            "unforgiving terrain concealing a cryptic tome ensconced a thousand feet beneath "
            "a crystalline mantle. Legion souls sought this relic's embrace, succumbing to"
            " its siren song. Eons drifted by, and at long last, humanity's dogged persistence"
            " bore fruit. Behold, the compendium that harbors the universe's enigmas and the "
            "very tapestry of divine wisdom. Empires clashed and conflagrations ignited"
            " as nations vied to possess this cryptic opus. Yet, destiny conspired to consign "
            "this priceless chronicle to the hands of a lad – Bruce by name. The "
            " epic of the tome's journey into his grasp is a saga deserving its own telling."
            ""
            "Bruce, transfixed by its verses, pored over the pages myriad times, each "
            "recitation an incredulous dance with enlightenment. In a bid to articulate the"
            " transcendence he'd experienced, he joined forces with celestial custodians who"
            " graced him under the cloak of night – yes, you heard right, ethereal"
            " beings in their seraphic splendor! From this communion between Bruce and"
            " the Angelic Host sprang forth the MyDiary App – a digital sanctum poised as"
            " the nexus between quotidian exploits and the numinous wellspring within."
            " Prepare to embark upon a sojourn where musings take flight, and spiritual insights "
            "take root. "
            ""
            "Venture forth with naught but audacious resolve, for our fortress of"
            " confidentiality is impenetrable. Engage in unbridled self-expression,"
            " unshackling the dam of thought to etch your innermost ruminations. Scribble,"
            " ponder, and peruse – for the act of inscription is a panacea, an elixir unto "
            "itself! Harness this tool to cultivate the bastion of your mental acumen, ascending"
            " towards empyreal echelons you've scarce fathomed."
    </string>

    <string name="revenuecat_sdk_key" translatable="false">goog_jlBEBqJeheOFjkNYbXZRxgEgroP</string>
    <string name="pricing_plan_monthly">Monthly</string>
    <string name="pricing_plan_monthly_cadence">/ Month</string>
    <string name="pricing_plan_yearly">Yearly</string>
    <string name="pricing_plan_yearly_cadence">/ Year</string>
    <string name="subscribe_button">Get Premium</string>
    <string name="restore_purchase">Restore Purchase</string>
    <string name="pricing_plan_offer_no_ads">Remove Ads</string>
    <string name="pricing_plan_offer_access_fonts">Access all stylish fonts</string>
    <string name="pricing_plan_offer_priority_on_support">Priority on support</string>
    <string name="pricing_plan_offer_add_images">Add Images to your entries</string>
    <string name="pricing_plan_best_value">Best Value</string>
    <string name="pricing_plan_screen_title">😊Get Premium</string>
    <string name="pricing_plan_screen_subtitle">Unlock all features of myDiary.Get the best experience by unlocking premium features.</string>

</resources>